valmont.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy

We recognize that visitors to our Web sites are concerned about how personal information they provide on-line is maintained and used by us. To address these concerns and to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy, we have developed and implemented this privacy policy so you will know how we gather and provide our information. Please review our privacy policy from time to time as we may update or change it periodically. 

**Gathering and Use of Information**   
We collect personally identifiable information from visitors to our sites solely on a voluntary basis. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, company name and/or telephone numbers (collectively referred to herein as "Personal Information"). We will never sell, transfer, or disclose any Personal Information we gather at our Web sites to any third parties without your prior consent, except in cases when we believe in good faith that we have a legal obligation to disclose such Personal Information. We never require that this Personal Information be provided in order to gain access to our sites, nor will we require visitors to disclose more Personal Information than is reasonably needed to participate in an activity on our sites. We collect Personal Information primarily for three reasons: 1) to e-mail customers with updates and news, 2) to notify winners of contests, games and sweepstakes, and to distribute prizes, and 3) to send out brochures, etc. via regular mail to subscribers. There may be times when we share aggregate information about our users (for example, the % of male and female visitors to our sites) with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties in any effort to customize or enhance the content and advertising on our sites for our users. 

**Contests/Sweepstakes**   
We may periodically run contests and sweepstakes on our sites for which we ask users/participants to provide contact information (like their e-mail address). This information is used to contact the participant when necessary in accordance with the rules of the contest or sweepstakes. 

**Cookies/IP Addresses**   
Like many companies, we may use "cookie" technology to track customer visits through our sites. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. They enhance the on-line experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. 

Any cookies we may use do not contain any personally identifying information and cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive. And although you may receive cookies from many different sites, each cookie can only be read by the Web server that originally issued it. You are not even identified by name or e-mail address, just by a unique string of numbers that we assign the first time you come to our site. 

We use your IP address in two ways: to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web sites, and also to gather broad demographic information. 

**Polls & Surveys**   
Information gathered from polls and surveys are only for our internal use. If sample answers to polls or surveys are posted on the Web site, then no identifiable Personal Information is ever included. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
Our sites will provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. Simply follow the procedure outlined at each site. Likewise, we will provide users with the opportunity to change any information previously provided. 

**How To Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the Legal Policy, the practices of this site, your dealings with this Web site, or your Personal Information, you can always contact us at our e-mail address, [webmaster@valmont.com](mailto:webmaster@valmont.com).
